(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
2023.12.29
Tsunomaki Watame
4th Anniversary LIVE
"Amazing Swing"
そのステージは "Lamb Vegas"
That stage is "Lamb Vegas"
誰もが魔法にかけられる
Everyone is put under a spell
忘れられない一夜をあなたに。
Giving you an unforgettable night.
It's showtime!
What a watame-zing night!
Yatcha no be-re-e night!
OK, follow me this rhythm of rhythm
What a what a stage!
満天 月が昇って
The full moon rises into the starry sky
光るネオンライト ネオンライト 夜が始まる
Shining neon lights, neon lights, the night begins
Me-Me- Night だって 月はもっと高望み
Even on a Me Me Night, the moon aims higher
落ち込み枕にダイブ なぜナンセンス
Diving into a pillow when depressed, why so nonsensical?
夢の中だけで見るなんてもったいないよね
It's a waste to only see it in your dreams, right?
お利口さんたちが眠ってる間にワナ・マーベラス
While the good kids are sleeping, I wanna marvelous
君も羊使いになりたいでしょ？
You want to be a sheep master too, don't you?
沈黙を壊すとどめはハイテクノロジー
The finishing blow to break the silence is high technology
溶けてるこの街
This melting city
What amazing
さながら宵の魔法
Just like the magic of the evening
Huwa Huwa Huwa
退屈な日常から連れ出してあげましょう
I'll take you away from your boring daily life
あからさまよいそのテンション
That blatantly good tension
Huwa Huwa Huwa
踊ろう 歌って
Let's dance, let's sing
この角巻バイブス
These Tsunomaki vibes
Da Da Da
街を楽しまなければ
If you don't enjoy the city
驚かせるなんてあり得ないから
You can't possibly surprise anyone
喜びのお裾分け for you ステージの上から
Sharing the joy with you from atop the stage
Hippie Hippie Ya Hippie Yay Hippie Ya
Sheep Sheep Ya Sheep Yay Sheep Ya
Let's go!
花吹雪 華やかな世界へおいで
A shower of petals, come to this brilliant world
お利口さんたちも夢中になれるワナ・マーベラス
Even the good kids can get hooked, I wanna marvelous
夜通しのスイングマジック 体を預けて
All-night swing magic, let your body go
落とし穴作っちゃうんでしょ 最初にダンス
You're probably making a pitfall, aren't you? Let's dance first
What an amazing swing!
甘え上手に誘われて Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
Tempted by a skilled coquette, Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
退屈なクラウドの日常から連れ出してあげましょう
Let me take you away from your boring daily life in the cloud
あからさま良い様テンション Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
An obviously high tension, Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
だだだって 煙立つ踊りまで Do-do-do-do-down
Because, because... until a smoky dance, Do-do-do-do-down
Do-do-do-do-down
Go for broke!
埃着飾ら見てまま ごちゃごちゃフロア転ばらぬトマササイズ
Decked out in dust, look as you are; the cluttered floor, no-fall Watama-cise
退廃的な大事実の劇だ 待機室も一流のフィクサーばかり
A decadent great truth's play; the waiting room is full of top-notch fixers
ギリギリ悪くない 尺八のような フワフワと跳ねるジャバ・ザ・ボラ
Barely not bad, like a shakuhachi, the Fuwa Fuwa jumping Java the Bora
太陽へ出すトーストするくらい 騒げ元旦 元旦 元旦!
To the point of toasting towards the sun, make some noise! New Year, New Year, New Year!
惑星を揺るがして
Shake the planet
音色な渦巻いて
Swirling with melodies
ステージは崩壊で
The stage is collapsing
Yeah, swinging per-night
浮かれな気持ちはマテロ Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
The festive feeling is Watamelo, Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
目映いラウドな非日常 どらに入れましょう
Dazzling, loud non-daily life; let's put it into the dorama
全てを退け出すテンション Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
A tension that drives everything away, Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa
いっそサンクチュアリ 輝く Do-do-do-do-down
May as well be a sanctuary, shining Do-do-do-do-down
Do-do-do-do-down
待ってた今に輝く Do-do-do-do-down
Shining in the moment we've been waiting for, Do-do-do-do-down
こんばんドドドー！
Konban-Dododo!
ドドド！
Dododo!
いらっしゃいませー、ラムベガスへー！
Welcome to Lamb Vegas!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ということで、角巻わため、4周年でございます！
So, it's Tsunomaki Watame's 4th anniversary!
みんな、いつも本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much everyone, always!
いやコメントもね、いっぱいありがとうございます。
And thank you for all the comments too.
「おめでとう」「おめでとう」、ありがとうー！
All the "Congratulations", thank you!
いや、みんなのおかげで、本当にここまで楽しく活動できたと思います。
I think I've been able to have fun activities until now, all thanks to you.
そこでみんなにお願いがあるんですけど、いいですか？
So, I have a request for everyone, is that okay?
えー、こちら、あの、こちら、
Well, this... um, this...
ハッシュタグが今日ありまして、
We have a hashtag for today,
「#角巻わため4周年」、4は半角でね、4周年。
"#角巻わため4周年", using a half-width "4" for the 4th anniversary.
ぜひいっぱいスクショとかを撮って、
Please take lots of screenshots,
たくさんポストとかしていただけたらなと思います！
and I'd love for you to post them a lot!
よろしくお願いします！
I'm counting on you!
えっちょっと見て、これ！
Hey, look at this!
ブーン、ブーン、ブーン、ブーン！
Vroom, vroom, vroom, vroom!
怒られないかなぁ？
I hope I don't get in trouble.
大丈夫かなぁ？
Is it okay?
あんまり振り回すとね、危ないですからね、
If I swing it too much, it's dangerous,
みんなも、しなりに気をつけてください。
so everyone, please be careful of the flex.
いや見て、これ！
Look at this!
ステージ！作っていただきました！
The stage! It was made for me!
イエーイ！
Yay!
これはね、「What an amazing swing」のMVですね、
This is from the "What an amazing swing" MV,
ミュージックビデオを再現していただいて、
it's a recreation of the music video.
え、すごくない？月とかね、かなりリアルにMVを再現してくれてて、
Isn't it amazing? The moon and everything look so real, just like the MV.
どうですか？
What do you think?
ここで今から、いっぱい歌って踊って、
I'm going to sing and dance a lot from now on,
楽しい楽しい宴をしていきたいと思ってますよ。
and have a fun, fun party!
準備はいいですか？
Are you ready?
あそこのステッキもね、見て！
And look at that cane (staff) too!
これ！
This!
あの、わためいとの毛をむしって作らせていただきました。
Um, I had it made by plucking the wool of Watamates.
いや、みんな毛の提供ありがとう！
Thanks to everyone for providing the wool!
こんなかっこいいステッキになりました、本当にありがとう、
It's become such a cool cane. Thank you so much.
いっぱい使いたいと思います、これからもね。
I want to use it a lot from now on.
いや、もうみんな待てないよね、
I'm sure everyone can't wait anymore.
「MC長い」って思ってない、大丈夫かな？
You might think the "MC is too long," I hope it's okay.
この後は、たくさんたくさん、ゲストの方と歌って踊ったりしていきますので、
After this, I'll be singing and dancing with many guests!
まだまだ盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's keep getting excited!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
寂しくて切ない一人の夜には
On lonely and painful nights spent alone
消えたい言葉を探して
Searching for words to make me disappear
秘密のドアを抜けてきて
Come pass through the secret door
君が Oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) Oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) Oh yeah!
And you, Oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) Oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) Oh yeah!
Shake it! 作詞・作曲: emon
Shake it! Lyrics & Composition: emon
バクタレです！
We're Bakutare!
そしてー！
And next...!
わため4周年おめでとう！
Watame, congrats on your 4th anniversary!
アゲてこうぜ！
Let's turn it up!
オウ！オウ！オウ！オウ！わため！レッツゴー！
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Watame! Let's go!
目の前の扉を開ければそう
If you open the door in front of you, yes
終わりのない夜への始まりだ
It's the beginning of a never-ending night
急上昇のフロアーの影から
From the shadows of the soaring floor
四次元への旅が始まるよ
The journey into the fourth dimension begins
流星の運ぶ船に乗ってさ
Riding on a ship carried by meteors
時空旅行へと...
On to a time-space journey...
いつだってフーフーさ
I'm always like "foo-foo"!
天気予報はアテにならないから
Since the weather forecast can't be trusted
気の向くまま　オーライ！
Just going with the flow, alright!
(オーライ！)
(Alright!)
Today is all night be funky funky funky night
You and I be together funky funky funky night
You and I funky night
上げてきな DANCE STEP キミの瞳から
Turn it up, DANCE STEP, from your eyes
輝きを奪う 流星群
A meteor shower that steals the sparkle
秘密のドアを 抜けてきて
Come through the secret door
You and I oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
shake shake 今夜は止まらない
shake shake, it's not stopping tonight
だから今は 夢の中
So for now, we're in a dream
ミラーボールが回り回る ハニー
The mirror ball spins round and round, honey
oh yeah! (oh yeah!) (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
DANCE DANCE キミの瞳から
DANCE DANCE from your eyes
shake shake 今夜は止まらない
shake shake, it's not stopping tonight
止まらない
Never stopping
上げてきな DANCE STEP キミの瞳から
Turn it up, DANCE STEP, from your eyes
輝きを奪う 流星群
A meteor shower that steals the sparkle
秘密のドアを 抜けてきて
Come through the secret door
You and I oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
shake shake 今夜は止まらない
shake shake, it's not stopping tonight
だから今は 夢の中
So for now, we're in a dream
ミラーボールが回り回る ハニー
The mirror ball spins round and round, honey
oh yeah! (oh yeah!) (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
寂しくたって 一人きりの夜には
Even if it's lonely, on those nights all alone
癒えない言葉 ボクが探して
I'll look for words that can't be healed
秘密のドアを 抜けてきて
Come through the secret door
You and I oh yeah! (Oh yeah!) (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
shake shake 今夜は止まらない
shake shake, it's not stopping tonight
だから今は 夢の中
So for now, we're in a dream
ミラーボールが回り回る ハニー
The mirror ball spins round and round, honey
oh yeah! (oh yeah!) (Yeah yeah yeah yeah)
全然つかめないキミのこと
I can't grasp anything about you at all
全然知らないうちに
Without me knowing it at all
ココロ奪われるなんてこと
That my heart could be stolen away
あるはずないでしょ
There's no way that could happen, right?
メランクリック
作詞・作曲：Junky
Melancholic
Lyrics & Composition: Junky
それは無愛想な笑顔だったり
Maybe it was that unfriendly smile
それは日曜日の日暮れだったり
Maybe it was that Sunday sunset
それはテストばっかの 期間だったり
Maybe it was those periods full of tests
それはキミという名の メランコリンニスト
It's a melancholinist by the name of "you"
手当たり次第強気でぶつかっても
Even if I hit you with everything I've got
なんにも手には残らないって思い込んでる
I'm convinced that nothing will remain in my hands
ちょっとぐらいの勇気にだって ちっちゃくなってふさぎ込んでる
Even at just a little bit of courage, I shrink and mope around
わたしだから
Because that's just how I am
全然つかめないキミのこと
I can't grasp anything about you at all
全然知らないうちに
Without me knowing it at all
ココロ奪われるなんてこと
That my heart could be stolen away
あるはずないでしょ
There's no way that could happen, right?
全然気づかないキミなんて
Someone like you who doesn't notice at all
全然知らない×知らないもん
I don't know you at all, I don't care
「ねえねえ」じゃないわ　この笑顔
It's not like I'm saying "Hey, hey", this smile
また眠れないでしょ
Now I won't be able to sleep again, will I?
明日も
Tomorrow too,
おんなじ
will it be the same
わたしが
me
いるのかな
who is here?
無愛想で
Unfriendly,
無口なままの
remaining silent,
カワいくないヤツ
and not at all cute.
あー
Ah—
あの夢にきみが
Ever since you appeared
出てきたときから
in that dream,
素直じゃないの
I haven't been honest.
じゃないの
I haven't,
だって
because...
全然つかめないきみのこと
I couldn't grasp a thing about you,
全然しらないうちに
and before I even realized it,
こころ奪おうとしてたのは
the one trying to steal a heart
わたしのほうだもん
was actually me.
ラララルラ...
La la lu la...
そういう時期なの
It's just that kind of season,
おぼれたいの
I want to drown in it.
いとしのメランコリー
My beloved melancholy.
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely
この夏は充実するの もっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling.
もう戻れなくたって忘れないで
Even if we can't go back, please don't forget.
summertime
何年経っても言えない
Even after all these years, I can't say it.
後悔したって構わない
I don't care if I end up regretting it.
でも言葉はここまで出てるの
But the words are right here on my lips.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
海岸通りを歩きたい
I want to walk along the coastal road.
ドライブだってしてみたい
I'd even like to go for a drive.
ただ視線を合わせてほしいの
I just want our eyes to meet.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
夜明けまで海辺走って
Running by the shore until dawn,
潮騒に包まれたいね
I want to be wrapped in the sound of the waves.
彼女の仕草が甘いね
Her gestures are so sweet, aren't they?
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely
この夏は充実するの もっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored dreamin' girl.
でも気持ちを伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I were to tell you my feelings, one day
この夢は覚めてしまうだろうな
this dream would probably come to an end.
青い影が揺れる街角
On the street corner where blue shadows sway.
占いなんて信じない
I don't believe in fortune-telling.
運命なんてあるわけない
There's no such thing as fate.
ただ本当のことを知りたいの
I just want to know the truth.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
近づく距離にも気づかない
Not even noticing how close we're getting.
胸の高鳴りごまかせない
I can't hide the throbbing in my chest.
でも昔と変わらずニブいの
But you're as dense as you've always been.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
思い出は色褪せたって
Even if memories fade,
惚れた腫れたの仲がいいね
it's nice to be so head-over-heels.
彼女の笑顔が憎いね
Her smile is just too much, isn't it?
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely
この夏は充実するの もっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored dreamin' girl.
でも気持ちを伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I were to tell you my feelings, one day
この夢は覚めてしまうだろうな
this dream would probably come to an end.
青い影が揺れる...
The blue shadows sway...
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely
この夏は充実するの もっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored dreamin' girl.
Ah...
噂のドリーミンガール 忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored dreaming girl
でも気持ち伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I convey my feelings, someday
この夢は醒めてしまうだろうな
this dream will surely come to an end.
青い影が揺れる街角
On the street corner where blue shadows sway,
Summertime
やあ、みんな！
Hi, everyone!
ラムベガス Amazing Swing 楽しんでますかー！？
Are you enjoying Lamb Vegas Amazing Swing!?
いやあ、バカタレサーカスでね、新曲と
Well, we had a new song with Bakatare Circus and...
これはもう、アゲアゲな曲を最初にね、ちょっとぶっ放したかったので
I really wanted to start off with some high-energy songs,
その選曲にさせていただいて、で、ぼたんちゃんとはメランコリック！
so I chose that setlist. And with Botan-chan, it was 'Melancholic'!
なんか甘酸っぱい、え、好きなの？ どうなくっついちゃうの？ え、どうなの？
It's a bittersweet one, like 'Do you like me? Are we getting close? What's going on?'
みたいな感じのね、甘酸っぱい曲を一緒に歌って踊らせていただきました！
We sang and danced to a bittersweet song like that together!
そしてなんと、ファウナとも！
And then, I performed with Fauna too!
え、初めてわための記念配信で3Dでね、一緒に歌って踊って
It was our first time singing and dancing together in 3D on my anniversary stream.
Summertime。ちょっとわためが、あの、男の子のね、パートをやらせていただいて
Performing 'Summertime', I took on the boy's part,
で、ファウナちゃんが女の子のパートをね、歌って踊っていただいて
and Fauna-chan sang and danced the girl's part.
どうだったかな？ どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
ちょっとね、やってみたかったんだよね。全部、楽しんでもらえてたら...
I've always wanted to try that. If you enjoyed it all...
楽しい？ 楽しい？
Are you having fun? Are you?
ありがとう！ 楽しい。圧じゃない、圧じゃないからね！
Thank you! 'Fun'. I'm not pressuring you, okay!?
ありがとうございます。でもまだまだ終わらない！
Thank you very much. But it's not over yet!
ここからゲストパート後半戦です！
Now for the second half of the guest segments!
うーん、楽しんでいこう！
Yeah, let's keep having fun!
リルビ 作詞・作曲：てにをは
Lilyby - Lyrics & Composition: teniwoha
ねえドクター、ヘッドクター メンテしておドクター
Hey Doctor, Head Doctor, please maintain me, Doctor
またいつもの例のバグが
That usual bug is back again
ハッピー、アラッキー、息々するもっと
Happy, unlucky, breathing more and more
組み立て全マイ、式の心、どこだ？
Assembled clockwork, where is the heart of the ceremony?
おかしいね、おかしいね、崩れないね イェイイェイ
It's strange, isn't it? It doesn't break, yeah yeah
わけないね、わけないね、ハイスペックなんで
It's easy, it's easy, because I'm high-spec
三千の保、やらなきゃさ
Three thousand maintenance tasks, I have to do them
ドキドキが止まりそう、ネジ巻いて
My heartbeat is about to stop, wind up the spring
なんていうか、エブリデイ ねじ巻いて ねじ巻いてよ
How should I put it, wind it up every day, wind it up
ちょっとだけね、ちょっちょちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just-just-just a little bit
ピーポパポ鳴らして 夢を作る
Beep-bo-ba-po, making a dream
ちょっとだけね、ちょっちょちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just-just-just a little bit
いまはまだ、止まっちゃいそう、そのうち
Right now, it feels like it's going to stop soon
なくなっちゃうかも、リルビ リルビ もっと
I might lose it, Lilyby Lilyby more
ねえドクター、メンテしたのドクター？
Hey Doctor, did you maintain me, Doctor?
Lalala...
自給の呪いなんて 払お
Let's cast away the curse of self-subsistence
なんだか、おっかないね、おっかないね、とんでもないね イェイイェイ
Somehow, it's scary, isn't it? It's incredible, yeah yeah
これはもう、テクノだ テクノロジーだ
This is already techno, it's technology
三連速だって 持ってるの
I even have triple speed
わかったらその手で すぐ巻いて
If you understand, wind it up with those hands right away
よわくても まだまだね ねじ巻いて ねじ巻いてよ
Even if I'm weak, I'm not done yet, wind it up, wind it up
ちょっとだけね、ちょっちょちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just-just-just a little bit
きみが、ミスっても笑わせてあげる
I'll make you laugh even if you make a mistake
ちょっとだけね、ちょっちょちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just-just-just a little bit
ほら、ドコドコドコドコ アップデートして
Look, update it everywhere
でもありがとう 心から リルビ リルビ
But thank you from the bottom of my heart, Lilyby Lilyby
ピーポパポ ピーポパポ
Beep-bo-ba-po, beep-bo-ba-po
くるくる しあわせ
Spinning happiness
起きて起きて 電子ひつじ
Wake up, wake up, electronic sheep
こちらに きやしゃんせ
Please come this way
その前に ひとまず ねじ巻いて
Before that, for now, wind it up
なんていうか、エブリデイ ねじ巻いて ねじ巻いてよ
How should I put it, wind it up every day, wind it up
ちょっとだけね、ちょっちょちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just-just-just a little bit
乙女、夢を作る
A maiden making a dream
ちょっとだけで 欲情 ちょっとだけで
Just a little lust, just a little bit.
NO バドラヴなんてもいいけど お日様 ちょっとだけ 待っててちょうだい
NO, bad love is fine too, but sun, wait for me just a little while.
ちょっとだけで ちょっとだけで
Just a little, just a little.
こんな毎日も 悪くないよ ちょっとだけで ちょっとだけで
Everyday like this isn't bad either, just a little bit, just a little.
でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち 足らなくなるかもね
But just a little bit might not be enough eventually.
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi
もー
More.
魅惑を隠す箱
The box that hides the allure,
秘宝に変わる危なげな
a dangerous thing that turns into a treasure.
デンジャラス 渡まりに滑る
Dangerous, sliding into Wata-Mari,
I'm Your Treasure Box
あーはーい！
Ahoy!
これ開けたらキミたちに何て言ってあげるべきかな？
What should I say to you when I open this?
探してたのは船長？
Was it the Captain you were looking for?
うーん、あーん！
Mmm, ahh!
そんなにガッついちゃダメだぞ。
You shouldn't be so greedy.
カラー お宝よりも魅力的なもの見つけちゃった？
Color, did you find something more charming than treasure?
いいじゃない！
Isn't that nice!
鎖骨がネットの赤
Clavicles are the red of the net,
極上の海賊の秘宝
the finest pirate treasure,
それは私
that is me.
あべこべ漂う香りも
Don't be afraid of
怖がらないで
the contrasting drifting scent.
開けてみて
Try opening it.
ははは！
(Laughs)
セクシー世界一 スーパーピチピチ
Sexy, world's best, super lively,
ぶっちゃけ全部捕まえたくない？
frankly, don't you want to catch it all?
You're gonna get treasure Maybe destiny
私の甘さが欲しいでしょ？
you want my sweetness, right?
あーはーい！秘宝の鍵を
Ahoy! Gently insert
優しく挿して
the key to the treasure.
あーはーい！この扉
Ahoy! Open this door,
マジで今すぐ開けて！
seriously, right now!
あーはーい！
Ahoy!
忍ばせた貴方の手
Your hand that was hidden,
掻き毟り甘い溜息のティー
scratching, sweet sighing tea.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
純度の薔薇が
Before the pure rose
萎れる前に
withers away.
Please stay with me
七つの大海を Marine with sheep
across the seven seas, Marine with sheep,
帆に風を受け進め
sail ahead with the wind.
Sailing!
寂しがり屋のマリン
Lonely Marine,
また手垢つけて何想像してんの？
what are you imagining with your handprints again?
No please grab me Marine's destiny
Open this box
Open eternal
Oh I will scream
開けて！
Open it!
鳴り止まぬ愛の殺意
Unceasing love's killing intent,
キミたちも我慢できたくない？
don't you want to be unable to hold back too?
淫らなオンパレード Maybe love for me
Lewd on parade, maybe love for me,
私の全てを手に入れて
take all of me.
禁忌の作法
Forbidden manners,
はしたない欲望
shameful desires.
シュワシュワな情事
Sparkling affair,
誰か助けて
someone help me.
マジで炎上しすぎ
Seriously, it's flaming too much,
キミたち何考えてんの？
what are you guys thinking?
分かってる渇望
I know your cravings,
だから今すぐ開けてよ
so open it right now.
宝箱
Treasure box...
貴方と繋がって
Connected with you...
キミたち、開けて！
You guys, open it!
スターライト
Starlight
作詞・作曲：DIVELA
Lyrics & Composition: DIVELA
描いた 未知のキャンバス
The unknown canvas I drew on
重ねる景色
Overlapping scenery
つないでみて 繰り返してく衝動
Try connecting them, the repeating impulse
揺らいだ 目の前に広がる世界
The swaying world spreading before my eyes
星屑のメロディ 歌に乗せてた
I put the stardust melody into a song
グッと鮮やかに 眩ませるように
Vividly, as if to dazzle
駆け抜けるよ スターライト
I'll dash through, Starlight
We can fly so! 僕らは いつしか
We can fly so! Before we know it, we...
夢の中惹かれて ただがむしゃらに 走り続けたよ
...were drawn into a dream, and just kept running recklessly.
無限の宇宙に 響いて
Resonating in the infinite universe,
君を照らす声は どこへだって
the voice that lights you up, anywhere...
ひらり 飛んでいけるさ
...it can flutter and fly!
愉快な 仲間と歩いた日日常
The happy days I spent with my friends,
掴んでみて 指先の意図せ
try grasping them, the intentions of my fingertips.
滲んでいく 目の前に広がった限界は
The boundaries that blurred before my eyes...
みんなの手重ねて ぶち壊して
...let's stack our hands and break them down!
吸い込まれそうな 夜空を見上げて
Looking up at the night sky that seems to suck me in,
今叫ぶよ スターライト
I'll shout out now, Starlight!
I wanna be so! 僕らは いつでも
I wanna be so! We will always...
そばで笑い合って 溢れる声が 遠く木霊する
...smile together, and our voices will echo far away.
願いのカケラ 灯して
Lighting the fragments of our wishes,
君の腕を引いて どこへだって
taking your hand, anywhere...
ひらり 飛んでいけるさ
...it can flutter and fly!
ちょっと不安な日も
Even on days when I'm a bit anxious,
魔法をかけてハッピー
I'll cast a spell and be happy!
百人力で乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome it with the strength of a hundred!
アクアブルーに染まる 大空目掛けて
Aiming for the vast sky dyed in aqua blue,
鼓動が弾んでいく
my heartbeat starts to bounce!
We can fly so! 僕らは
We can fly so! We...
この日をずっと待ってたんだ
...have been waiting for this day forever!
まだ覚めないで
Please, don't wake up yet!
スターライト！僕らは 止まらない
Starlight! We won't stop!
その光が消える 1秒前まで 走り続けよう
Let's keep running until one second before that light fades out!
無限の宇宙に 響いて
Resonating in the infinite universe,
君を照らす声を 強く抱いて
holding the voice that lights you up tightly...
きらり 輝いていけ！
...go and shine brightly!
いやあ！楽しいねえ！
Wow! This is fun!
やあゲストパートもね、一区切りつきまして
Well, the guest part has come to a close,
このロボ子ちゃんとマリンちゃんとスバルちゃんという
with Roboco-chan, Marine-chan, and Subaru-chan,
かなり珍しい組み合わせだったのではないでしょうか
which I think was a pretty rare combination.
でもね、もうずっとずっと呼びたいと思ってたね、みんなだからね
But you know, they're all people I've wanted to invite for a long, long time,
こうやって一緒に歌って踊って
so being able to sing and dance together like this,
なんかね、セクシーな感じもね、出せたりとか
and showing a bit of a sexy side,
かっこいい感じも出せたりとかね、してたよね？
as well as a cool side... we did that, right?
セクシーじゃない、してたよね？
Not sexy? We did it, didn't we?
あれはセクシーだったよね、みんな
That was sexy, wasn't it, everyone?
ま、ね、いろんな、まあ、わためをちょっと見てもらえたんじゃないかなーと思っております
Well, I hope you were able to see various sides of Watame.
まあ、もうね、活動4周年ですから
I mean, it's already my 4th anniversary,
ちょっと成長した姿もね、見せたいなーなんて思って
so I wanted to show you a slightly more grown-up side of myself.
今フェロモン出てるから
I'm putting out pheromones right now.
見せたいなーなんて思って、頑張りました
I wanted to show you that, so I did my best.
いやーどうだったかな、楽しんでくれてるよね？
I wonder how it was... you're enjoying it, right?
いやー、わためはとっても楽しいです。いやめちゃくちゃ楽しい
Man, Watame is having so much fun. It's incredibly fun.
こうやって3Dになって、衣装も...
Becoming 3D like this, and with this outfit...
だいぶ増えたよね。
They've increased quite a bit, haven't they?
こうやってみるとね。
When you look at it like this.
いや、なんかその衣装も増えたことによって
Well, with the increase in costumes,
隣にこう、メンバーと立って
standing next to other members like this,
なんかこう、シナジーというか、
there's some kind of synergy, or...
なんか... なんだろうね。
some... what is it?
なんかね、いいよね。
It's nice, isn't it?
語彙力。
My vocabulary.
語彙力はちょっと、5年目磨きたいなと思います。
I'd like to polish my vocabulary in my fifth year.
いや、でもまだまだここでは終わりませんので、
But it's not over yet,
えー、この先もぜひ見てほしいなと思っています。
so I hope you'll continue watching.
いや、それもあれなんだよ。
Also, there's that thing.
サムネ見ていただけたかな。
I wonder if you saw the thumbnail.
ま、見てるよね。待機中とかね。
Well, you probably did. While waiting and all.
多分見れるもんね。
You can probably see it.
そうだよね。ホロジュールとか載ってるもんね。
Right. It's on Holodule and stuff.
あの文字見ましたか。
Did you see those words?
し、ん、い、しょう、なんかお披露目があるとか。
"N-e-w c-o-s-t-u-m-e" unveiling, or something.
それも、ま、もう後半戦だから、ね、あったりするんじゃないかな。
That might be happening since it's the second half now.
ね、見たいよね。
You want to see it, right?
いや、お願い、見て、お願い見て。
Please, watch it. Please watch.
頑張るんで。
I'll do my best.
見てほしいなと思います。
I hope you'll watch it.
では、ふぅ、落ち着いてね。
Now, *whew*, let me calm down.
よし。
Alright.
では、次の曲聴いてください。
Now, please listen to the next song.
RAINBOW。
RAINBOW.
RAINBOW
作詞・作曲 DECO*27
Lyrics/Music: DECO*27
ねえ 「おはよう」のあと
Hey, after saying "good morning,"
もう落ち込んでるの？
are you already feeling down?
ああ やりたいことも
Ah, the things I want to do,
怖い 叶え夢にしたい
they're scary, but I want to make them dreams come true.
もうちょっとだけの自分
Just a little bit more of myself,
もう一歩が踏み出せない
I can't take that one extra step.
そう言えばオッケーだった
It was okay to say that,
逃げていられた
I could keep running away.
でも君が笑って
But if you smile
「それでもいい」と言うんだったら
and say "that's okay too,"
恥ずかしいところとか
the embarrassing parts of me,
ダメダメなところとか
the useless parts of me,
見せたくなくなっちゃうでしょう
I won't want to show them anymore, right?
どんな時も前を向いて歌っていたい
I want to keep singing while facing forward, no matter when.
ほら凹んで泣いて辛い時も
Look, even when I'm feeling down, crying, and having a hard time,
強がってるけど平気だよ
I'm acting tough, but I'm fine.
きっと君のためならできること
I'm sure it's something I can do for your sake.
涙を大好きにばら撒いて
Scattering my tears into the things I love,
弱くたって虹を呼び出せるよ
even if I'm weak, I can call forth a rainbow.
明日も多分僕次第で
Tomorrow will probably be up to me,
今日よりも輝いていく
and I'll keep shining brighter than today.
ねえ 「おはよう」のあと
Hey, after saying "good morning,"
なんだか気分がいい
I feel somehow good.
もう 「繰り返し」とか
No more "repetitions,"
ない そう思えるよ
none; I can feel that way now.
意外と怖くないね
It's not as scary as I thought.
あくまで個人の感想です
*This is just my personal opinion.*
秘められた力とか
Hidden powers,
見たことない奇跡とか
unseen miracles...
そんなのも妄想しちゃうかも
I might even fantasize about things like that.
用意ドンで僕は変わる
I'll change at the "Ready, Go!"
合図は君に出してほしい
I want you to give me the signal.
大冒険する準備なら
If it's preparation for a great adventure,
ちゃんと君の分までしておいたよ
I've already done your share too.
どんな時も前を向いて歌っていたい
I want to keep singing while facing forward, no matter when.
ほら凹んで泣いて辛い時も
Look, even when I'm feeling down, crying, and having a hard time,
強がってるけど平気だよ
I'm acting tough, but I'm fine.
きっと君のためならできること
I'm sure it's something I can do for your sake.
涙を大好きにばら撒いて
Scattering my tears into the things I love,
弱くたって虹を呼び出せるよ
even if I'm weak, I can call forth a rainbow.
明日も多分僕次第で
Tomorrow will probably be up to me,
今日よりも輝いていく
and I'll keep shining brighter than today.
La la la...
WataMeister
作詞・作曲・編曲：剣持秀文
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Kenmochi Hidefumi
期待のルーキーはシープなホープ
The promising rookie is a sheepy hope
その頭のホーンがさらにキュート
Those horns on her head are even cuter
このくるくる巻いてるクールなムーブに
With these curling, cool moves
売るほどあるぜ良質なウール
I've got high-quality wool to sell
ハサミでチョキ　バリカンでスー
Snip with scissors, buzz with clippers
あったか毛布直販でーす
Direct sales of warm blankets!
なんと今日お買い上げいただくと
If you buy today, believe it or not
さらにもう一個ついてきまーす
You'll get one more for free!
混迷する混紡の世界
In the chaotic world of blended fabrics
鮮やかに救う救世主
A savior who saves vibrantly
コットン　リネン
Cotton, linen
レーヨンにアクリル　シルク
Rayon, acrylic, silk
ナイロンにポリエステル
Nylon and polyester
一方こちら天然のウール
On the other hand, here's natural wool
合成繊維戦意喪失
Synthetic fibers lose their will to fight
元気ない奴はここに来な
If you're feeling down, come here
こころの綿パンパンにしてやんよ
I'll stuff your heart full of cotton!
よく晴れた日　光浴びて
On a sunny day, soaking in the light
膨らませよう心の綿毛
Let's puff up the fluff in our hearts
寒い日には　温めるよ
On cold days, I'll warm you up
それがわたくしわための役目
That is my, Watame's, duty
白い雲に似せて
Resembling white clouds
こんな広い空に
In such a wide sky
浮かべたらどうでしょう
How about letting them float?
眠れない夜は私の名を呼んで
On sleepless nights, call my name
素敵な夢に一名様をご招待
I'll invite one guest to a wonderful dream
眠れない夜は私を思い出して
On sleepless nights, remember me
楽しい夢にみんなまとめて連れて行くよ
I'll take everyone together to a fun dream
わたマイスター
WataMeister
カチカチのザラメが進化した
Hard granulated sugar has evolved
最高の魔改造
Into the ultimate modification
色とりどりのふわふわの夢
Colorful, fluffy dreams
詰め込まれている奇跡のお菓子
A miraculous sweet packed full of them
わためのわたがしなら食べ放題だぜ
If it's Watame's cotton candy, it's all-you-can-eat!
☑ この業務用マシンの
☑ スペックなら
☑ 1日で2本の
☑ ハイスピード製造OK
☑ For this industrial machine's
☑ specs
☑ 2 pieces a day
☑ High-speed production: OK
この業務用マシンのスペックなら
With the specs of this industrial machine
１分で２本のハイスピード製造OK!
High-speed production of 2 per minute: OK!
行列のできるわたあめ屋
The cotton candy shop with a queue
道のりは長い　険しく　甘くない
The road is long, rugged, and not sweet
溶けたザラメに　とろけるフレーバー
Melting sugar with melting flavor
カラフルな色で　無数の創造性
Countless creativity in colorful hues
宇宙に輝く星々にも似た
Resembling the stars shining in space
割り箸でつかむ輝く宝石
A shining gem gripped by chopsticks
町内会の縁日の祭りに
At the neighborhood association's festival
欠かせない必須アイテム参上
An essential item makes its appearance
甘い香りにのせて
Carried on a sweet scent
こんな広い空に
In such a wide sky
浮かべたらどうでしょう
How about letting them float?
愉快な仲間と同じ時過ごして
Spending time with pleasant friends
気が付いたらだいぶ遠くまで歩いてた
I realized I'd walked quite a long way
いつもみんながいたから
Because everyone was always there
支えられてここまで来ました
I was supported and made it this far
お礼と言ってはなんですが
It's not much of a thank you, but...
さん、はい！
One, two!
眠れない夜は私の名を呼んで
On sleepless nights, call my name
素敵な夢に一名様をご招待
I'll invite one guest to a wonderful dream
眠れない夜は私を思い出して
On sleepless nights, remember me
楽しい夢にみんなまとめて連れて行くよ
I'll take everyone together to a fun dream
わたマイスター
WataMeister
あー、どうだったかな。
Ah, I wonder how it was.
Rainbow、そして新曲のWataMeisterという曲を
Rainbow, and then the new song WataMeister...
歌わせていただきました！
I performed them!
いや、なんとね、WataMeister、
Well, you see, WataMeister,
こちら作詞・作曲・編曲が
The lyrics, composition, and arrangement for this one
剣持秀文さんにお願いした曲になりまして、
were handled by Kenmochi Hidefumi,
ちょっとね、歌詞とかも不思議な感じがあったかなと思うんですけど、
and I think the lyrics had a bit of a mysterious feel to them.
こちらアルバムに入ってます。
This is included in the album.
Hop Step Sheepに入ってますので、
It's in Hop Step Sheep,
ぜひたくさん買っていただいて、聴いてほしいなと思います。
so please buy many copies and give it a listen.
なんていうか、まだあるよね。
How should I say this... there's still more, right?
まだまだあるよね。
There's still more and more.
わ、わための姿が...
Whoa, Watame's appearance...
変わっちまったー！
has changed!
ということで、こちら100万人記念で
So, to commemorate 1 million subscribers,
新しい3Dのお衣装を作っていただきました！
a new 3D outfit was created for me!
いや、みんなのおかげでこの衣装を着ることができたんだよ。
I was able to wear this outfit thanks to everyone.
本当にありがとう。
Thank you so much.
チャンネル登録とかもたくさんありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for all the subscriptions.
そしてね、おめでとうもいっぱいありがとうね。
And thank you for all the 'congratulations'.
本当にみんなが作ってくれた衣装と言っても過言ではありません。
It's no exaggeration to say this outfit was made by everyone.
ゆっくり見せてもいいかな？
Can I show it to you slowly?
いい？
Is it okay?
こだわりポイントいい？ちょっとだけ、いいかな？
Can I show the special points? Just a little bit?
まず、靴、見てみて！
First, look at the shoes!
かっこいいよね。
They're cool, right?
今回はね、スポーティな、そしてダンスも結構踊ったりするので、
This time it's sporty, and since I'll be dancing quite a bit,
ダンスしやすいそんな衣装を頼みました。
I asked for an outfit that's easy to dance in.
いや、すごい。
Wow, amazing.
そして太ももの...見る？太もも。
And the thighs... wanna see? The thighs.
ふー、ふー、むちむちな感じがね。
Phew, phew... that plump feeling.
ちょっとライブなのに、変態みたい...
I'm like a pervert, even though it's a live concert...
あとはね、尻尾！
And then, the tail!
なかなかね、わための衣装的に尻尾は見えないんだけどね、
Usually, Watame's outfits don't show the tail, but
今回はガッツリ丸見えでございます。
this time it's in full view.
あとは...わきぺーもあります！
Also... the armpit point is here too!
ふー！
Whoo!
素晴らしい。この筋が素晴らしいね。
Wonderful. These muscle lines are great.
この筋がね。
These lines right here.
あと髪型もね、
Also the hairstyle,
ちょっとサイドポニーと言いますか、高いところからのポニーテール。
it's a side pony, or rather, a high ponytail.
このクシュッとなってんだよね、頭の上がね。
It's all fluffy on top of the head.
どうですかー？
How is it?
可愛いかな？
Is it cute?
こちらもね、フェミ満々に仕立てていただきました。
This was also made to be very feminine for me.
でもね、まだこれだけでは終わらないんだよね。
But, it's not over with just this.
へへへ、何だと思う？
Hehehe, what do you think?
あー、おー。
Ah, oh.
そう、わためはまだ変身をあと一つ残しているのだ。
Yes, Watame still has one more transformation left.
見たい？
Wanna see?
じゃあちょっと着替えちゃおうかな。
Then I think I'll change for a bit.
そして、あの曲もね、まだ終わりじゃないので、
And also, that song isn't over yet,
聴いてほしい曲がもう一曲あります。
so I have one more song I want you to hear.
まだまだ盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's keep the excitement going!
では、次の曲聴いてください。
Now, please listen to the next song.
スレスレ 波打つカップの上
On the edge, on top of the waving cup
ズレズレ もつれた拍子の上
Out of sync, on top of the tangled rhythm
ドドドド ドライブして
D-D-D-D-Driving
ギギギギ ギア入れて
S-S-S-S-Shifting gears
パパパパ と片付けて
Cl-cl-cl-cl-Cleaning up
さぁ踊りましょう
Now, let's dance
誰よりも没頭 もっと
More immersed than anyone else, more
点々はドット ドッド
The dots are dots, dots
今すぐにダイビング
Diving right now
飛び込んでけ
Jump in
ダダダダダダ ダンシング ただ踊って
D-D-D-D-D-D-Dancing, just dancing
ママママ 満身創痍なったって
E-e-e-e-even if I'm covered in wounds
捨て身で Step
With a leap of faith, Step
すれ違って
Passing by
おー！ 踊っちゃって
Oh! Dancing
ジャジャジャジャ ジャンケンポンで勝っちゃって
W-w-w-w-winning at Rock-Paper-Scissors
ケケケケ ケンケンパ進んじゃって
H-h-h-h-hopping forward
かまって可能性 感じちゃって
Fee-fee-fee-fee-feeling the possibility
ふたりの Now step
Our Now step
徒然 半分ビートの上
Leisurely, on top of the half beat
それぞれ ゆらしてこの場所で
Shaking in our own ways in this place
スススス スライドして
S-s-s-s-Sliding
ツツツツ 爪弾いて
P-p-p-p-Plucking
今晩も
Tonight as well
さあ踊りましょう
Come on, let's dance
音鳴らせ　もっともっと
Let the sound ring, more and more
神様は　ゴッドゴッド
God is... God God
楽しみたいなら
If you want to have fun
フロアへ直行
Go straight to the floor
ダダダダダダダ　ダンスまだ踊っちゃって
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da dance, keep on dancing
カカカカ関係ない　朝まで
I-I-I-I-it doesn't matter, until morning
ステステップ滑っても　気にしないで
Ste-step, even if you slip, don't worry about it
オッケー！踊っちゃって
Okay! Just dance
ザザザザ斬新ただ笑っちゃって
Za-za-za-za novel, just laugh
テテテテ天然だってハッピーで
Te-te-te-te naturally happy
回って万能性　感じちゃって
Spin around and feel the versatility
つまり Now on step
In short, Now on step
おーおー　踊ってる？
Oh oh, are you dancing?
おーおー　ゆらいでる？
Oh oh, are you swaying?
ミラーボールが回ってる
The mirror ball is spinning
もっと踊ってたい
I want to dance more
おーおー　踊ってる？
Oh oh, are you dancing?
おーおー　踊ってよ
Oh oh, dance with me
終わりが来るまでずっと
Until the end comes, always
踊りあかそう
Let's dance the night away
誰よりも　もっともっと
More than anyone, more and more
満点は　ドットドット
The perfect score is... dot dot
今すぐにダイビング　飛び込んでけ
Dive in right now, jump in
ダダダダダダダ　ダンスただ踊ったって
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da dance, even if you just dance
ママママ満身創痍になったって
Ma-ma-ma-ma even if you're covered in wounds
ステステ捨て身で　すれ違って
Ste-ste risk it all and pass each other
オッケー！踊っちゃって
Okay! Just dance
ジャジャジャジャジャンケンポンで勝っちゃって
Ja-ja-ja-ja winning at rock-paper-scissors
ケケケケケンパ進んじゃって
Ke-ke-ke-ke moving forward in hopscotch
かまって可能性　感じちゃって
Feel the possibility of being cared for
つまり Now on step
In short, Now on step
おーおー　踊ってよう
Oh oh, let's dance
おーおー　踊ってよ
Oh oh, dance with me
おーおー　踊ってよう
Oh oh, let's dance
おーおー　踊ってよ
Oh oh, dance with me
おーおー　踊ってよう
Oh oh, let's dance
おーおー　踊ってよ
Oh oh, dance with me
おーおー　踊ってよう
Oh oh, let's dance
おーおー　踊ってよ
Oh oh, dance with me
ふわー！みんな今日は本当にありがとう！
Whew! Everyone, thank you so much for today!
とっても楽しかったよー！
It was so much fun!
新曲の「Now on step」という曲を歌って躍らせていただきました。
I sang and danced to my new song, "Now on step."
これはね、みんなにぜひサビの振り付けを踊ってもらいたいなと思って、ひろみ先生に振り付けを作っていただいたので
I wanted everyone to dance the choreography of the chorus, so I asked Hiromi-sensei to create the choreography...
一緒にたくさん踊って騒ぎましょう、これからも！本当にありがとう。
...so let's all dance and have fun together from now on! Thank you so much.
4周年か…早いなあ。
Four years, huh... Time flies.
でもこう、ずっと笑顔を絶やさず…まあ泣いたりもするけど
But, you know, keeping a smile on my face... well, I do cry sometimes too...
でも、楽しく本当に今もこうしてわためが動き回れているのも
But the reason why Watame can move around like this happily...
みんなのおかげだと思っておりますので、本当に感謝！ありがとうございます。
...is all thanks to everyone, so I'm truly grateful! Thank you very much.
今日初めて知ってくれた人も、今までずっと応援してくれてる人も
Whether you found out about me today or you've been supporting me all along...
これからは5周年に向けて、まだまだ怒涛の羊頑張っていきますので
From now on, heading towards my 5th anniversary, this unstoppable sheep will continue to do her best...
どうぞ応援よろしくお願いします！本当にありがとう！楽しいこといっぱいこれからもしていきましょう。
...so please continue to support me! Thank you so much! Let's keep doing lots of fun things from now on.
おっ、このあと色々告知もあるので、チャンネルはそのままでお楽しみに！
Oh, there are various announcements coming up, so stay tuned to this channel!
さらにそのあとの面ゲンでは、この新衣装の上着バージョンもゆっくりお披露目したり
And in the members-only stream after this, I'll be showing off the jacket version of this new outfit...
歌ったりしていきたいなと思ってますので、みんなぜひ遊びに来てください！
...and I'm thinking of doing some singing too, so please come and visit!
今日は本当にありがとう！これからもよろしく！
Thank you so much for today! I look forward to your continued support!
改めまして、4周年ライブ見てくれてありがとうございました！いや楽しかったね！
Once again, thank you for watching the 4th anniversary live! It was so much fun!
今回は、初披露のオリジナル楽曲を2曲も発表できて嬉しいです。
I'm happy that I could announce two original songs that were performed for the first time.
まず最初の1曲目は「Wata Meister」という曲で、作詞・作曲・編曲を剣持英郁さんにお願いしました。イエーイ！
The first song is called "Wata Meister," and I asked Kenmochi Hidefumi-san to write the lyrics, compose, and arrange it. Yay!
「ハサミでチョキ　バリカンですー」というね、面白いワードも入っていたり、サビではエモい部分もあったり
It includes interesting words like "snip with scissors, buzzed with clippers," and the chorus has some emotional parts too...
聞くのが心地よい曲かなーと思うので、
I think it's a very pleasant song to listen to,
ぜひ、わためのアルバム「Hop Step Sheep」をゲットして
so please get Watame's album 'Hop Step Sheep'
何度でも聞いてください！
and listen to it over and over again!
そして、最後に歌った楽曲は
And the song I sang at the very end,
「Now on step」という楽曲で
is a song titled 'Now on step',
この楽曲は以前にも「乙女のうたとわなる未来」という
and it was composed by Sato Yosuke,
曲を作っていただいたことがある
who previously worked with me on the song
佐藤陽介さんに制作していただきました！
'Otome no Uta to Wanaru Mirai'!
みんなと一緒に歌って踊って楽しめる曲になってますので、
It's a song we can all sing and dance to together,
1月31日のセカンドライブで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！
so let's have a blast at the 2nd Live on January 31st!
この後すぐ、「Now on step」のMVも投稿されるので、
The MV for 'Now on step' will be posted right after this,
ぜひ見てください！
so please check it out!
サビの振りもショート動画を上げる予定なので、
I'm also planning to upload a short video of the chorus choreo,
練習よろしくお願いします！
so please use it to practice!
そして、なんとこの後24時から
Also, surprisingly, starting from midnight tonight,
楽曲配信もあります！
the song will be available on streaming services!
「Now on step」たくさん買ってください！
Please buy 'Now on step' a lot!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you in advance!
穴が開くほど聴いて、
Listen to it until your ears fall off,
振りもたくさん練習して
and practice the choreography a lot,
1月31日、めちゃくちゃ楽しいライブにしましょう！
and let's make the January 31st live an amazing one!
そんな31日、もう一回おさらいです！
Now, let's recap the details for the 31st once more!
角巻わため 2nd Live
Tsunomaki Watame 2nd Live
「わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER」が
'Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER'
来月の1月31日にあります！
will be held next month on January 31st!
チケット販売リンクや特設サイトなど
Ticket links, the special website, and more
概要欄に記載してあるので、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
are in the description, so please check them out!
配信チケットなどあります！
Streaming tickets are also available!
そしてななななんと！
And, and, and...!
全国の書店とのコラボキャンペーンが開催決定！
A bookstore collaboration campaign nationwide is confirmed!
対象書店でお買い物時にノベルティをプレゼントさせていただきます。
You'll receive a novelty gift when shopping at participating stores.
ノベルティには描き下ろしミニキャライラストやメッセージが入っており、
The novelties feature new mini-character art and messages,
対象書店ではライブのキービジュアルを使用したポスターが掲示されたり、
and participating stores will display live key visual posters,
さらに一部の書店では角巻わための楽曲や
and some will even broadcast Tsunomaki Watame's music
特別な店外音声も放送されます！
and special in-store announcements!
実施期間は2024年1月12日から、
The campaign runs from January 12th, 2024,
ライブが開催される1月31日まで。
until the day of the live, January 31st.
企画の詳細や対象店舗はこの後公開される
For more details and participating stores,
ほんのひきだしの記事をチェックしてみてください。
please check the 'Hon no Hikidashi' article coming soon.
まだまだ告知があります！
I still have more announcements!
角巻わため 4周年記念グッズが
Tsunomaki Watame's 4th Anniversary Goods
この後販売されます！
will go on sale shortly after this!
詳細はこちら！
Here are the details!
まずはBIGメガネ置きアクリルスタンド！
First, the BIG glasses holder acrylic stand!
いやーこれは可愛すぎませんか？
Wow, isn't this just too cute?
わためなりきりサングラスも掛けられます！
You can even put the 'Watame sunglasses' on it!
もちろんメガネも掛けられますので、
Of course, regular glasses work too,
一家に一台、二台、三台いかがでしょうか？
so how about one, two, or even three for your home?
こちらのイラスト、なんとふーみ先生描き下ろしとなります！
This illustration was newly drawn by Fuumi-sensei!
ふーみママ、いつもありがとう！
Fuumi-mama, thank you as always!
イラストが可愛すぎちゃって置くだけでも癒やされそうだよね。
It's so cute that just having it there is healing.
お次はノート＆ペン！
Next is the Note & Pen set!
おださやか先生描き下ろしのA6サイズノートです！
It's an A6 size notebook drawn by Oda Sayaka-sensei!
いや、これも可愛いなー。
Man, this one is cute too.
おだ先生がキャラクターデザインを担当されているゲームがわため大好きでして、
I love the games Oda-sensei does character designs for,
過去にもわためのグッズで描いていただいたことがあるんですが、
and although she's drawn for my goods before,
今回も快く4種類のわためを描いてくださいました！
she kindly drew four different Watames for us again!
ペンの方はクリックをするたびに
As for the pen, every time you click it,
わためのセリフやわためいとの表情が変わる仕様になっているので、
Watame's lines and the Watamates' expressions change,
その時の気分に合わせてクリックしてみてください！
so click away depending on your mood!
いっぱい使ってね。
Please use it a lot.
最後はわためナンバーワンタンブラー！
Finally, the 'Watame Number One Tumbler'!
おしゃれなデザイン！
What a stylish design!
そして熱いのも、冷たいのもいけちゃいます！
And it works for both hot and cold drinks!
もちろん蓋も付いています！
Of course, it comes with a lid too!
つまり最強ということです！
In other words, it's the ultimate tumbler!
みんなこのタンブラーでわためとおそろっちしましょう！
Let's all have matching tumblers with Watame!
そしてフルセットを購入していただいた方には、
And for those who purchase the full set,
角巻わため箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りの
you'll get a heart-shaped die-cut postcard
ハート型ダイカットポストカードと
with a foil-stamped signature and message,
特典ボイスがついてきます！
plus a special bonus voice track!
ぜひフルセットで手に入れてください！
Please consider getting the full set!
いや、ここまでどどどっと告知をさせていただきましたが、
Whoa, that was a lot of announcements all at once!
まとめると、この後「Now on step」のMVが上がります！
To recap: first, the 'Now on step' MV goes up next!
そして角巻わため4周年記念グッズ販売開始します！
Then, 4th Anniversary Goods go on sale!
そして、その後メン限ライブがあります！
And after that, there's a members-only live stream!
さらに24時からは「Now on step」の楽曲配信があります！
Plus, 'Now on step' hits streaming at midnight!
こんな感じかな？言いそびれてないかな？
I think that's it? Did I forget anything?
あとライブも来年あります！という感じで。
Oh, and the big live concert is next year! That's the gist.
これからも嬉しいこととか
I want to keep sharing many more happy things
みんなも喜んでくれるようなことをたくさん共有していけるように
and things that make you all smile from here on out.
頑張っていきたいと思っているので、
I'll keep doing my very best,
5年目も一緒に歩いてくれると嬉しいです！
so I'd be happy if you walk with me through my 5th year too!
これからもよろしく！
I'm counting on you!
楽しいことはまだ終わらねぇ！
The fun doesn't end here!
この後の新曲MVや、全編ライブも楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's enjoy the upcoming new song MV
and the full live concert!
みんなね、バタバタすると思いますが、
I'm sure you'll all be busy getting ready,
わためは全編ライブの準備をしてきますので、またそこで会いましょう！
...but I'll be preparing for the full concert,
so I'll see you there!
では、また後ほど！
Well then, see you later!
これからもよろしくね！
I look forward to your continued support!
わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
2024.1.31 Wed.
Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
Amazing Swing
角巻わため 3D新衣装お披露目 ＆ 重大告知あり！
Tsunomaki Watame 3D New Outfit Reveal
& Major Announcement!